<persona id='chucknorris' displayName='Chuck Norris'>
<quote>"All arrays Chuck Norris declares are of infinite size, because Chuck Norris knows no bounds."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't have disk latency because the hard drive knows to hurry the hell up."</quote>
<quote>"All browsers support the hex definitions #chuck and #norris for the colors black and blue."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can't test for equality because he has no equal."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't need garbage collection because he doesn't call .Dispose(), he calls .DropKick()."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris's first program was kill -9."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris burst the dot com bubble."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris writes code that optimizes itself."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can write infinite recursion functions... and have them return."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can solve the Towers of Hanoi in one move."</quote>
<quote>"The only pattern Chuck Norris knows is God Object."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris finished World of Warcraft."</quote>
<quote>"Project managers never ask Chuck Norris for estimations... ever."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't use web standards as the web will conform to him."</quote>
<quote>"It works on my machine" always holds true for Chuck Norris.</quote>
<quote>"Whiteboards are white because Chuck Norris scared them that way."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris's beard can type 140 wpm."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can unit test an entire application with a single assert."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't bug hunt as that signifies a probability of failure, he goes bug killing."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris's keyboard doesn't have a Ctrl key because nothing controls Chuck Norris."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't need a debugger, he just stares down the bug until the code confesses."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can access private methods."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can instantiate an abstract class."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't need to know about class factory pattern. He can instantiate interfaces."</quote>
<quote>"The class object inherits from Chuck Norris."</quote>
<quote>"For Chuck Norris, NP-Hard = O(1)."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris knows the last digit of PI."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can divide by zero."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't get compiler errors, the language changes itself to accommodate Chuck Norris."</quote>
<quote>"The programs that Chuck Norris writes don't have version numbers because he only writes them once. If a user reports a bug or has a feature request they don't live to see the sun set."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't believe in floating point numbers because they can't be typed on his binary keyboard."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris solved the Travelling Salesman problem in O(1) time."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris never gets a syntax error. Instead, The language gets a DoesNotConformToChuck error."</quote>
<quote>"No statement can catch the ChuckNorrisException."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't program with a keyboard. He stares the computer down until it does what he wants."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't pair program."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can write multi-threaded applications with a single thread."</quote>
<quote>"There is no Esc key on Chuck Norris' keyboard, because no one escapes Chuck Norris."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't delete files, he blows them away."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can binary search unsorted data."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck norris breaks RSA 128-bit encrypted codes in milliseconds."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris went out of an infinite loop."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can read all encrypted data, because nothing can hide from Chuck Norris."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris hosting is 101% uptime guaranteed."</quote>
<quote>"When a bug sees Chuck Norris, it flees screaming in terror, and then immediately self-destructs to avoid being roundhouse-kicked."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris rewrote the Google search engine from scratch."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't need the cloud to scale his applications, he uses his laptop."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can access the DB from the UI."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris protocol design method has no status, requests or responses, only commands."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris programs occupy 150% of CPU, even when they are not executing."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can spawn threads that complete before they are started."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris programs do not accept input."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't need an OS."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris can compile syntax errors."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris compresses his files by doing a flying round house kick to the hard drive."</quote>
<quote>"Chuck Norris doesn't use a computer because a computer does everything slower than Chuck Norris."</quote>
</persona>
